i think i'm entering a stage of doing
more videos
i'm under the awareness that i either
have multiple ideas and i can't choose
between them which um makes me not take
action
or no idea and i'm gonna honor when i
have no idea but when i have multiple
ideas
pick one and just do it and let the
other ones fall by the wayside
so i've had this these
things happen to me over the last couple
weeks that i wanted to share with you
and in order to share them i need to
share a concept that i've learnt over
the last few weeks called the glimmer
when when you have autism you have more
things that trigger you everyone has
things that trigger them
but i have sight smells and sounds that
trigger my nervous system
and make me go into overdrive and i
don't like them and they have sensations
in my body they don't like
the flip side of that is glimmers the
sights the sounds the smells that
lift up my heart and soul in the moment
and i seek those things out
some of them are stimming like being on
swings and some of them
are these smells and so in the forest
that i go for a walk-in
they've cleared out this patch of trees
and their cedars they've cut down
and so every time i go for this walk i
go and walk up to this one tree and
smell it and a couple week about a week
ago i realized
how perfect it was that it was exactly
at nose height like i just
literally walk right up to it it's like
right here
and i was like oh if they done it
further down i have to bend down and
that would hurt my lower back
it was just something cool and it wasn't
the force the force didn't cut itself
off at that
at that stage right it was the the
loggers but that's the kind of thing
that um if i told someone about it like
that's a coincidence it's not a sign
from the universe for anything
um and that's the point it's like a
personal miracle
it proves it to me when these things
happen over and over again it's not
about proving it to anyone else because
they're like mundane miracles
it's you have to look for yours in your
life not someone's in someone else's
life right theirs is never gonna prove
it to you and if it does it's probably
about um trying to be something instead
of just being something
right if i'd went and cut that cedar
plank off and then like hey look i mean
the tree trunk so on this walk that i've
been doing for years
i only realized a few months ago was
definitely during the pandemic
that there's a swing set and i'd love
swing sets every time i see one if it's
any kind of if it's any kind of large
swing set
i need to go on it and so now when i go
on this walk every day i go on the swing
set
and it's only been a few months but in
the last few weeks i've had these things
occur every time i'm on the slight walk
out of the way to get to the swing set
or on the swing side itself
and so i don't remember what order they
happened in but i remember one of the
times just seeing a dragonfly on the way
and dragonflies are
my insect animal that i will see from
nature when there's a message
and i don't even know what the message
is it's not like the dragonfly is like
all right
now do your taxes like it's like it's
not a direct
uh courts of action it's just like
nature in my in my belief system it's
nature just telling me she has my back
like yeah
we see you we know what you're doing
here's a gift
and so like if i came on and told you
about the dragonfly weeks ago i'd be
like
yeah great but in that same section i've
had these
multiple things happen so then i was
sitting on the swings
about a week ago and a coyote crossed
the road and went to the
went to the forest and i know when i see
a coyote it's huge it's not quite like a
dragonfly coyotes are very rare the
other time i saw one where it was a
message it was on my birthday and it was
right outside my house
it was like 9 30 in the morning when
coyote shouldn't be out this was closer
to
seven in the morning and so
just amazing that the coyote was there
right then one of the other times right
after
uh it was one or two days it was right
before right after that one
there was this these little songbirds
that were like right in front of my
my face doing their little dance they
weren't just flying by it was like right
in front
doing this dance and then took off and
went away
and then yesterday when i was sitting on
the swing
listening to my music air singing like i
do
because it's about like going out and
feeling good that's why i'm there
to like respark my to glimmer and um
all of a sudden i got this overwhelming
smell of cedar
that the forest doesn't really give off
it kind of only gives it off when it's
cut but it was just and it's far enough
away from the forest that it's i'm not
surrounded by trees and it was just this
and i
it i get um like phantom smells
sometimes
but they last like a second like it's
not very long and this one lasted like
30 seconds a minute i was like wow oh my
goodness this this
it's the smell that comes up and the
other thing that has felt drops of rain
i'm like it's sunny out it can't be
raining
and then it started raining more and
more and there was like no rain anywhere
else
like i could see off in the distance and
it was just while i was on the swing
and it was my favorite weather which is
when it's sunny out and raining at the
same time
and nearly it was just like for the
length of a song and then i got off
and it was just like oh thank you and i
knew that that was the message to tell
you
this this so i was gonna do this one
yesterday but
doing it today because i want to know
from you
what are your messages that the universe
or nature
or god whatever you call it the mystery
that is the reason we are here
is giving you and to start waking up to
them because even just like again those
they're not concrete this is what you do
it's just
yeah we see you you're on the right path
you're doing it
you're doing it right or sometimes it's
the opposite you know when you see it
is this like a glimmer or trigger is
this something yes you're doing right or
doing wrong
and that's what i'm here to do is figure
out my best course of action and my
learning and growth
and and take my very tailored
education system the universe is giving
me my tailor-made course
and i invite you to do the same so i
would love to know your glimmers the
things that make you happy
and make your heart sing as well as if
you have
had any signs from the universe in the
last few weeks
and what they are if you want to share
them you can share them in the comments
below
and read other people's if they've
commented and i'm sure i will be on here
more often because today is day one no
pot for the month august 1st
right thank you and i will see you later